Aaron Zomback

Hello, I'm Aaron. I'm a product designer with full-stack web development skills and experience. Before becoming a designer and coder, I developed a strong background in biochemistry through my education and professional experience. Now jumping into technology, I'm excited to expand my career scope into <u>UX design and software development.</u> My ultimate goal is to improve science education and accessibility through user-interface design.

3 Chemin du Gage Chazay-d'Azergues, France aaronzomback@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance UX designer, Chazay D'azergues, FR

March 2020 - present

I've been hired to work for a variety of successful clients, from designing a food takeout app for a start-up, a boutique t-shirt company, to redesigning a restaurant point-of-sale system. My complete portfolio can be found at www.zomback.design. I am also an active member of the Interaction-Design Foundation.

Calder Biosciences, Brooklyn, NY — Sr. Research Associate Scientist

November 2014 - October 2019

Designed and conducted experiments targeting vaccine candidates for HIV, RSV (Respiratory Syncytial Virus) & Influenza.

EDUCATION

SuperHi, online courses

December 2019 - May 2020

Visual Design & Branding, Intro to User Experience, Foundations HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Ruby-on-Rails

University of Washington, Seattle, WA — *Biochemistry B.S.*

September 2009 - June 2014

Distinction: awarded Mary Gates Research Scholarship for host-virus research work in Dr. Harmit Malik's lab.

PROJECTS

TimeSink[™] — A web app for an online cinema platform

Designing and developing an online platform for filmmakers to present their work and receive user reviews. I am writing the application using Ruby on Rails.

FILMS

SKILLS

CODING

HTML/CSS/Javascript/Ruby on Rails foundational coding knowledge and applications.

UX/UI DESIGN Building interactive mobile/web prototypes in Figma. Other deliverables include: user-flows, empathy mapping, user research, SWOT competitive analysis, site maps, google analytics, et al. It's all about the process, knowing which tools to use, and how the story is told.

VIDEO motion effects and graphics editing using Adobe After Effects. Expert with Adobe Premiere Cs6+

communication strong experience in working with clients to achieve their business goals. I have strong experience presenting scientific data, collaborating with other researchers and colleagues, & planning strategies to achieve business objectives.

Software Applications strong knowledge in a suite of tools: GraphPad Prism 6,
SeqBuilder, Excel, Word,
Powerpoint, Figma,
Photoshop, Premiere Pro.

LABORATORY experimental design and execution, safety protocols, mastery of tools such as pipettes, filters, TFF & column purifications,

Sovereign Blue — 2018, short film

My second short film that I created while I was living and working in Brooklyn, NY - I wrote, produced, and directed this short, featuring Rodney Ferrer as the maniacal CEO of a multi-media company. A review of the film can be found here at UK Film Review.

Expanded Metal — 2016, short film

My first short film that I created. It later went on to screen at the 2017 Philip K. Dick Science Fiction film festival in New York City.

measurements, inventory, note-taking, and analysis.

AWARDS

Mary Gates Research Scholarship Viral & Host Protein Interaction Research

LANGUAGES

English (native), Spanish (proficiency), French (learning)